aheadworks.com 2019-07-17

# Privacy Policy | Aheadworks - A Magento Development Company

### General information

We respect your right to privacy. This policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy.

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.

Aheadworks, Inc. (hereinafter referred to as “we“ or „data controller“) is a provider of Magento extensions or other products. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ecommerce.aheadworks.com (“Site) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User"). This privacy policy applies to the Site, any and all products and services offered on ecommerceaheadworks.com. For the purpose of this Site, the “User” shall be any person entered onto the Site, including, but not limited to, subscribers to our newsletter, and the “Client” shall be any person who has registered with the Site. The terms of these privacy policies apply to you whenever you access the content and / or service we provide, regardless of which device (computer, cell phone, tablet, TV, etc.) you use.

Data contoller: Aheadworks, Inc.

Registered office: 16192 Coastal Highway, Lewes, Delaware, United States, 19958

Phone: [+375173005582](tel:+375173005582)

E-mail: [helpdesk@aheadworks.com](mailto:helpdesk@aheadworks.com)

We hereby confirm that your personal data shall be collected in accordance with the requirements of the legal acts of the European Union, the United States of America and the instructions of the controlling authorities. All reasonable technical and administrative measures shall be applied in order to protect your personal data from loss, unauthorized use and / or changes of data.

Persons under the age of 16 cannot provide any personal information through our site / social networking accounts. If you are a person below the age of 16, before submitting personal information, you must obtain a consent of your parents or other legal guardians.

The terms used in these rules are understood as defined in the General Data Protection Regulation No. 2016/679 (EU).

It is very important that you carefully read these privacy policies, because each time you visit this Site, you agree to the terms described herein. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not visit our Site, do not use our content and / or services. Click on “Find out more” in each section to find detailed information about the processing of your personal data and the specifics of our business.

### How do we collect information about you?

Your personal data, e.g. any information about you that allows us to recognize you is collected in various ways: 

  * you may provide us with information directly (e.g. filling in a registration form, creating an account, submitting order, filling helpdesk tickets, etc.);
  * we may collect information automatically (e.g. when you access our website, social account);
  * we may acquire information from third parties and collect information about you from publicly available sources (e.g. through Facebook, LinkedIn social network, your company website or otherwise).

### What information about you do we collect?

Registration: Your name, last name, telephone number, country, account creation date, email, VAT number, billing address, order number and date, invoice number and date, SKU (items), support period, VAT amount, payment method, payment transaction ID.

User content: Texts, photos, vector and other images and similar.

Google Analytics: Aheadworks, Inc. is using Google Analytics to track standard user data on traffic sources, visitor behavior flow, audience overview. We may use your user ID to track specific behavior, however, it cannot be connected to other data we are collecting about the users.

Server logs and Cookies: When you access our services online, our web servers automatically create records of your visit. These records typically include IP-address, access times, the sites linked from, pages visited, the links and features used, the content viewed or requested, browser or application type, and other information of such kind. See also our Information on Cookies usage below.

### Where do we store your personal data?

Please be informed that we store your personal data in digital format in a datacenter located in St. Louis, Missouri.

### For what purposes do we use information about you and on what legal basis?

Subject to the above, information is processed for the following purposes: 

  * to create account;
  * to administer a sale;
  * to address the customer`s problem concerning Helpdesk tickets;
  * to provide information, which was requested by you, related to the provision of services;
  * for marketing purposes, e.g. to provide tailor-made advertisements and promotional content and to send reports about promotional activities, to evaluate and analyze market, customers, products and services (including collecting your opinion on products and services, organizing customers / partners surveys, contests or promotional activities to the extent permitted by law);
  * to find out how people use our online services in order to improve them and create new content, products and services;
  * to defend our interests in court or in other institution.

  * compliance with legal obligations to which we are subjects;
  * a legitimate business interest that is not overridden by interests you have to protect the information;
  * in certain cases, your consent.

### Who do we share your information with?

We may share information about you: 

  * with companies that provide services on our request;
  * with companies that help organize marketing provision (eg. Mailchimp);
  * with other responsible selected business partners;
  * with other third parties, where required or permitted by law, or is necessary to protect our legitimate interests;
  * with other entities upon your consent.

### Where might information about you be sent?

When using information as described in this notice, information about you may be transferred either within or outside the country or territory where it was collected, including to a country or territory that may not have equivalent data protection standards. In such cases, we do our best to ensure the security of your personal data being transmitted.

### How do we protect information about you?

We adopt effective and appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. However, keep in mind that while we are taking appropriate action to protect your information, no website, online transaction, computer system or wireless connection is completely safe.

### How long will information about you be kept?

We will retain information about you for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the information was collected. After that, we will delete it, unless applicable legal acts obliges us to store information for tax purposes, or data may be required for pre-trial investigation, but in any case, the retention period will be no more than 3 years. When this term expires, the data will be deleted in such a way that it cannot be restored.

### What rights do you have?

The data subject whose data is processed by the data controller, depending on the situation, has these rights: 

  * to be informed about personal data being processed (right to be informed);
  * to access personal data and get information about how personal data is being processed (right to access);
  * to obtain from the controller the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning data subject and have the right to have incomplete personal data completed (right to rectification);
  * to erase personal data or suspend data processing activities (except storage) (right to erase and right to be “forgotten”);
  * to require the data controller to restrict the processing of personal data for one of the legitimate reasons (right to restriction of processing);
  * to transmit personal data to another controller (right to data portability);
  * to object at any time to processing of personal data concerning data subject which is based on the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the controller or by a third party. In order for the controller to process personal data, he is responsible to prove that the processing is conducted for legitimate reasons and those reasons are beyond the interests of the data subject;
  * lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority in your country.

We offer you easy ways to exercise these rights. You can do this by writing to us at [helpdesk@aheadworks.com](mailto:helpdesk@aheadworks.com), or by using certain links at the bottom of the promotional content provided by us.

We may not give you the conditions for the implementation of the above mentioned rights, where in the cases provided by the law, it is necessary to ensure the prevention of crimes, offenses of professional or ethical conduct, as well as to ensure the protection of the rights and freedoms of the data subject or other persons.

### Cookies, signals and similar technologies

In this Privacy Policy we use the term “cookies” for cookies and other similar technologies, such as Pixel Tags, Web Beacons, clear GIFs, etc.

### Final provisions

This Privacy Policy applies for this Site and Magento Marketplace. Users may find content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our Clients, partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. This Site may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

We have the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will inform you about such changes and the most up-to-date version of this policy.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [helpdesk@aheadworks.com](mailto:helpdesk@aheadworks.com). This Privacy Policy is subject to the Law of the United States of America.

Data protection officer can be reached at: [settlement@aheadworks.com](mailto:settlement@aheadworks.com) or by phone [+37166016251](tel:+37166016251)

This document was last updated on March 11, 2019.
